seahawks.com 2013-10-14

# Privacy Policy

**Updated: October 29, 2012**

This privacy policy applies to the Seattle Seahawks' website located at www.seahawks.com and our companion site <http://www.centurylinkfield.com/> the "Website". The purpose of this privacy policy is to disclose to you what information we may collect, how we may collect it, with whom we may share it, and certain other matters related to such information, including the choices you have regarding our collection of information and our use and disclosure to other parties of information we may have collected from you. Most information collected from our visitors will occur on or from our main site www.seahawks.com and limited information is collected on our companion site <http://www.centurylinkfield.com/>; however our privacy practices remain consistent for both Web sites.

Seattle Seahwaks has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html)  including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers information collected through this Web sites, www.seahawks.com and /www.centurylinkfield.com . TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [customerservice@seahawks.com](mailto:customerservice@seahawks.com).  If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here.](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint)

When this privacy policy uses the term "personally identifiable information" or "personal information," we mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as your full name, street address or email address. When other information, such as a favorite team or player, is associated with personal information, it also becomes personally identifiable information for the purposes of this privacy policy.

Please read the information below to learn more about our data collection policies and practices.

  1. [Types Of Information That May Be Collected](http://www.seahawks.com/about/privacy-policy.html#types)
  2. [How Information May Be Collected](http://www.seahawks.com/about/privacy-policy.html#howcollected)
  3. [How We Use The Information Collected](http://www.seahawks.com/about/privacy-policy.html#howweuse)
  4. [With Whom The Information May Be Shared](http://www.seahawks.com/about/privacy-policy.html#whowesharewith)
  5. [Chat Rooms, Forums, And Message Boards](http://www.seahawks.com/about/privacy-policy.html#chatrooms)
  6. [Links To Other Websites](http://www.seahawks.com/about/privacy-policy.html#linkstoother)
  7. [A Special Note For Parents Concerning Privacy](http://www.seahawks.com/about/privacy-policy.html#parents)
  8. [Security](http://www.seahawks.com/about/privacy-policy.html#security)
  9. [Notification Of Changes And Your Acceptance Of The Privacy Policy](http://www.seahawks.com/about/privacy-policy.html#acceptance)
  10. [Correcting/Updating Personal Information](http://www.seahawks.com/about/privacy-policy.html#correcting)
  11. [Data Retention](http://www.seahawks.com/about/privacy-policy.html#dataretention)
  12. [Your California Privacy Rights](http://www.seahawks.com/about/privacy-policy.html#california)
  13. [Questions About This Privacy Policy](http://www.seahawks.com/about/privacy-policy.html#questions)

**TYPES OF INFORMATION THAT MAY BE COLLECTED**

The following are the types of information we may collect:

Information You Provide Us: In the course of using the website, we may ask you to provide us with certain information, including contact information, such as your name, mailing address, email address and phone number; unique identifiers, such as your user id and password; information regarding others such as your child's name and age, emergency contact information, or friend's name and email address and financial information, such as your credit card number or similar information. IP Address and click stream data. See "IP Addresses and Click Stream Data" section below.

Site Usage Information: We may receive and store certain types of internet usage information whenever you visit the Website, such as your IP Address and click stream data. See "[ **IP Addresses and Click Stream Data**](http://www.seahawks.com/about/privacy-policy.html#ip)" section below.

We use a third party to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. The third party may also collect anonymous information about your visits to our web site. This is primarily accomplished through the use of a technology device, commonly referred to as a Web beacon or an Action Tag, which we place on various web pages within our web site* that allows the third party to collect anonymous information. The third party may use information about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide ads about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by the third party, " **click here**." The third party reports the anonymous data that they collect on our behalf back to us, which we link to our customer's personally identifiable information for the purposes of better serving you. When we merge this data, it is treated under this policy as personally identifiable information as described above.

**HOW INFORMATION MAY BE COLLECTED**

We may collect information from you in several different areas on the Website, including but not limited to those described below:

_Purchases or transactions_  
You may be asked to complete a registration form and provide personally identifiable information; you may also be asked to choose a user ID and password in order to take advantage of certain features the Website may choose to offer, such as access to your order history and account information. Participation in registration is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website.

_Newsletters and Website Emails_  
We offer free newsletters to share information with you about the Website, about us and our affiliates and subsidiaries, or about our marketing partners and advertisers and sponsors. You may receive a newsletter either by registering for a particular newsletter or in conjunction with a special feature or membership for which you have registered on the Website. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website. You may also cancel your free email subscription by following the instructions provided on the Website or in the newsletter or email. The Seahawks use a third party to facilitate the collection of personal information when signing up for newsletter or subscription emails. You may opt-out of receiving further email subscriptions by signing into your Ticketmaster account and changing your subscription preferences. This information is shared back with the Seahawks in order to facilitate the email communications. Please see the "With Whom The Information May Be Shared” below. You may also send an email to [**customerservice@seahawks.com**](mailto:customerservice@seahawks.com) to have your name removed from any mailing list.

_Contests or Sweepstakes_  
We periodically operate contests and sweepstakes through the Website that may require registration or the submission of personal information. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website. Your personally identifiable information may be used to contact you for winner notification, prize delivery confirmation or other related purposes, (see the rules of each contest for details about how your personal information will be used). We may also ask your permission to allow us to publicly post some of your information on the Website, such as on a winner's page, in the event you win a contest or sweepstakes. Except as required by applicable law, we will not post your information without your permission. In some instances, a third party advertiser or sponsor may operate or host a contest or sweepstakes on the Website, and collect your information. In those cases, where we are not the operator or host of the contest or sweepstakes, we do not collect your information and we have no control over the information collected from you. Accordingly, we urge you to review the advertiser's or sponsor's privacy policy applicable to the contest or sweepstakes before participating.

_Surveys or Voting_  
From time-to-time we may request personally identifiable information from you in conjunction with a survey or voting poll. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website.

_Cookies_  
As with many Websites, our Website uses a technology called "cookies." A cookie is a unique, random number that is stored in the browser on your computer. The cookie doesn't actually identify you, just the computer that is used to visit the site. Cookies automatically identify your browser to the Website whenever your computer is used to visit the Website. Cookies also let us know how many people visit our website and where visitors go on the site. In addition, cookies can let us know non-personally identifiable information, like what web browser is being used to access the website. For registered users, cookies can make using the Website easier for you by saving information such as your passwords or preferences. By tracking how and when you use the Website, cookies help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the Website are based on data obtained from cookies. Accepting cookies allows you, among other things, to personalize your experience on the Website. Cookies may also allow the Website to present to you advertising which may be of interest to you. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, your browser should contain an option that allows you to disable or delete cookie data at any time. Some areas of the Website, however, may not provide you with a personalized experience if you have disabled the use of cookies.

_Web Beacons and Other Tracking Technology_  
Our Website uses a variety of technical methods for tracking purposes, including Web beacons. Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of Web sites. We also use these technical methods to analyze the traffic patterns on our Web sites, such as the frequency with which our users visit various parts of our Web sites. These technical methods may involve the transmission of information either directly to us or to another party authorized by us to collect information on our behalf. We also use these technical methods in HTML e-mails that we send our guests to determine whether our guests have opened those e-mails and/or clicked on links in those e-mails. The information from use of these technical methods may be collected in a form that is personally identifiable.

_IP Addresses and Click-Stream Data_  
We may collect IP addresses and/or click-stream data. An IP address is a number associated with the service through which you access the Internet, like your ISP (Internet service provider), your company, or your university. Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, we also use IP addresses for purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers and sponsors, for example regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of our sites. We may combine this information with personally identifiable information. Click-stream data is information collected by our computers when you request Web pages from the Website. Click-stream data may include such information as the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of browser making the request, the preceding page view and other such non-personal information. When analyzed, this data helps us analyze how visitors arrive at the Website, what type of content is most popular, what type of visitors in the aggregate are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising, and the like.

_Third Party Providers and Use of Cookies_  
Seahawks.com works with a variety of third party providers to serve website ads and keep track of site analytics. Google Analytics and Omniture are utilized to keep track of aggregate site traffic. Traffic numbers are not tied to personal information. Information about your visits to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you. For more information about DoubleClick, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please [click here](http://www.dbleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy) or paste this URL into your web browser - <http://www.dbleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy> . In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

The use of cookies by our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] is not covered by our privacy policy.  We do not have access or control over these cookies.  Our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] use session ID cookies [to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order for you to use the shopping cart, etc.] 

You can leave this in here is you are still using Ominiture and Google Analytics or you can use the disclosure below which is more generic and covers all third party cookies.

_Widgets_  
Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

_Transaction Information_  
If you conduct a financial transaction with our Website, such as placing an order through our pro shop or registering for an event, we will ask you to complete an order form that will request certain information from you, including contact information, demographic information and financial information. We will use this information to complete the transaction that you have requested, i.e., to deliver the information, products or other services that you order, and to invoice you. For your protection, such information is collected and stored through encrypted means.

**HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED**

As applicable, the information you provide to us may be used to:

  * contact you about the Website;
  * contact you relating to your membership status, in response to your request for more information, or regarding an employment application;
  * confirm or fulfill an order you have made;
  * inform you of a prize you have won;
  * monitor or improve the use of the Website;
  * customize the advertising and content you see;
  * monitor compliance with our terms and conditions of use of the Website; and
  * send you promotional material or special offers on behalf of our marketing partners and/or their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties.

**WITH WHOM THE INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED**

At times, we may share with or have a third party directly collect your personal information for various purposes. The following outlines the ways in which this may occur in relation to activities on our site and the ways in which you may opt-out of having your information shared:

Agents: We employ other businesses, certain services and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, removing repetitive information from customer lists, Website analysis, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They may have access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for their own purposes, like sending you marketing offers about their products.

When purchasing tickets online, registering as a season ticket holder or inside subscriber visitors will be linked to [www.ticketmaster.com](http://www.ticketmaster.com/) to facilitate these functions. All personal information collected in these areas are done so directly by Ticketmaster and not the Seattle Seahawks. Certain personal information collected by Ticketmaster may be shared back with the Seahawks in order to fulfill a request, such as when signing up for email communications through Seahawks Insider. Please refer to the Ticketmaster privacy policy for more information regarding their personal information collection practices.

In some instances, you may be linked to an outside Web site where the pages may display the Seatlle Seahawks branding or look and feel of the Seahawks Web site. Some of these areas may include applying for our team logo credit card and similar activities. Please note that you are submitting your information directly to these third party sites even though these pages have the look and feel of our team site. It will be clear on these pages the entity collecting your personal information and you should refer to the privacy statement available from these pages.

Aggregate Information: We may share aggregate information, such as demographics and Website usage statistics, with advertisers, sponsors or other organizations. When this type of information is shared, the other parties do not have access to your personally identifiable information.

Subsidiaries and Affiliates: We do not share personal information with any third parties for marketing purposes.

Third-Party Ad Serving & Audience and Traffic Measurement Services: The Website may use a third party network advertiser to serve the advertisements on the Website or may use a traffic measurement service to analyze the traffic on the Website. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to this Website and other Websites you have visited. Third-party ad serving enables us to target advertisements to you for products or Websites you might be interested in. Audience and Traffic Measurement Services allow us to collect anonymous traffic and behavior information from our Website by monitoring anonymous visitor activity. Although advertisers or other companies do not have access to the Website cookies, the Website's advertisers, sponsors and/or traffic measurement services may themselves set and access their own cookies on your computer if you choose to have your cookies enabled in your browser. Cookies allow third party advertisers to show you advertisements or content you might be interested in. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Please click visit <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx> in order to learn more about the information collection practices and "opt-out" procedures of third party ad servers we may use. To learn more about analytics software used please visit <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>.

Business Transfers: In the event that all or substantially all of our assets are sold or transferred to another party, or another transaction occurs in which your personally identifiable information is one of the business assets transferred, all personally identifiable information that has been collected and saved may be one of the business assets we transfer. See "[Your Acceptance of the Privacy Policy and Notification of Changes to the Policy](http://www.seahawks.com/about/privacy-policy.html#9)" section below.

Administrative or Legal Process: Your personal information may be transferred to third parties without notice to you in order to comply with applicable law ,such as to comply with a subpoena, law enforcement agencies, to protect our rights, or protect the rights of other users of this website.

**CHAT ROOMS, FORUMS, AND MESSAGE BOARDS**

The Website may make chat rooms, forums and message boards available to its users. You are not required to provide any personal information when using these areas but you may choose to do so. If you post personal information online, it will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. We cannot ensure the security of any information you choose to make public in a chat room, forum, or message board. Also, we cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these areas. Any areas of the site where visitor/fan photos are displayed along with their personal information, permission from those submitting pictures was obtained prior to the posting on the Web site. To request removal of your personal information from our community forum, contact us at [email or direct the user to contact information].  In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**

You should be aware that when you are on the Website you could be directed to other Websites beyond our control. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, the "click" may take you off the Website onto a different Website. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and marketing partners that may use the Website's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other Websites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. If you visit a Website that is linked to our Website, you should consult that Website's privacy policy before providing any personal information.

**SECURITY**

This Website incorporates reasonable safeguards to protect the security, integrity, completeness, accuracy and privacy of the personal information that we may collect and we have put into place reasonable precautions to protect such information from loss, misuse and alteration. Your personally identifiable information is transferred to our computers utilizing encryption software. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to do their jobs are allowed access. Our security policies are reviewed periodically and revised as required.

When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

**A SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS CONCERNING PRIVACY**

The Website is a general audience Website. Although we have a section of our site geared toward children, we do not collect any personal information directly from children under the age of thirteen on the Website. If in the future, we collect personally identifiable information from children, it will do so in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (15 U.S.C. 6501 et seq.) including, without limitation, obtaining necessary parental consent.

The Internet offers children wonderful educational and entertainment resources. Your guidance and involvement are essential to help ensure that children have a safe and rewarding online experience. We encourage you to visit the Direct Marketing Association's Web Website ([www.the-dma.org](http://www.the-dma.org/)) and explore the Get CyberSavvy! Program as well as the GetNetWise Website ([www.getnetwise.org](http://www.getnetwise.org/)) to learn more about parental control tools.

**YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE PRIVACY POLICY AND NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES TO THE POLICY**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any change in how we use your personal information we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**CORRECTING/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your email address or zip code), or if you no longer desire to access our Website, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update, delete  or remove the personal data you have provided to us.

For information collected within the Pro Shop, you may access your collected information by logging into your account and changing your information.

For information collected by Ticketmaster, you may access your Ticketmaster account through the Tickets section of our Web site to make any corrections or change your email preferences.

You may also contact us at [customerservice@seahawks.com](mailto:customerservice@seahawks.com) regarding information collected in otherareas of our Web site.

**DATA RETENTION**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account     or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [email address].  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

Under California law, our customers that are California residents may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. As detailed above, we do not share our customer's personal information with unaffiliated third parties for direct marketing purposes without their approval.

If at any time you wish to opt out of having your personal information shared with third parties and/or receiving information from Seattle Seahawks (via e-mail or postal mail) about new products, services, or promotions, you can do so. You may contact us at Seattle Seahawks contact info (12 Seahawks Way Renton, WA 98056). You can also contact us by e-mailing us at [customerservice@seahawks.com](mailto:customerservice@seahawks.com). Please indicate what publications or services you no longer wish to receive so that we may better address your needs.

**QUESTIONS ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the privacy practices of this Website, contact [customerservice@seahawks.com](mailto:customerservice@seahawks.com).

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to:

Attn: Website Privacy Policy  
12 Seahawks Way  
Renton, WA 98056
